{
	"Title": "Round 1: Soundtracks! Movie title, song title & composer/artist please. 1 point for each.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Star Wars (John Williams & London Symphony Orchestra - Star Wars)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:7a9UUo3zfID7Ik2fTQjRLi",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Gladiator (Hans Zimmer, Lisa Gerrard, Klaus Badelt, Gavin Greenaway & The Lyndhurst Orchestra - Now we are free)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:11IXRdEjiH0KL8nh4G1j7d",
          "Offset": 28000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Back to the future (Huey Lewis & The News - The power of love)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:2olVm1lHicpveMAo4AUDRB",
          "Offset": 62000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Highlander (Queen - Who wants to live forever)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:3SGP8It5WDnCONyApJKRTJ",
          "Offset": 169400,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Lord of the Rings (Howard Shore & Enya - The council of Elrond (Theme for Aragorn & Arwen))",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:3Knohqfb9jeYzL6wMZiWLM",
          "Offset": 37000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Intouchable (Ludovico Einaudi - Fly)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:4yLSpYlcO0jPPLTa3nW8zN",
          "Offset": 120000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Jurassic Park (John Williams - Theme from Jurassic Park)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:2TZbQZXOuR8osP2AK8yYMN",
          "Offset": 157000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "The Imitation Game (Alexandre Desplat & London Symphony Orchestra - The Imitation Game)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:0o9ivTBX7mjTnaUYF4Gk6t",
          "Offset": 40000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "James Bond - Skyfall (Adele - Skyfall)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:6VObnIkLVruX4UVyxWhlqm",
          "Offset": 125000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "4 weddings and a funeral (Wet wet wet - Love is all around)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "spotify:track:0PCGfA36HrVPmsBZJ57zOU",
          "Offset": 60000,
          "Duration": 10000
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
